Southern California Women for Understanding (SCWU) collection, 1975-1999
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Area chapters., 1979-1997.; Series 6.; 123.0 folders
  - Los Angeles/Valley., 1979-1994.; Subseries 4.; 58.0 folders
    - Committees., 1980-1993.; 3 folders (Box 12, Folders 55 - 57)
      Folder 57: Steering (1980-1985)
    - Committee: Education - Welcome to our Lesbian World printed materials., 1982-1983.; 18 folders (Box 12, Folders 35 - 52, 61 - 62)
      Folder 61: Correspondence (1983)
      Folder 62: LA/Valley Chapter- Education Committee- Welcome to Our Lesbian World: Photographs
      Folder 35: Minutes (undated)
      Folder 36: Production planning (1982)
      Folder 37: Stage manager notes (undated)
      Folder 38: Scripts (undated)
      Folder 39: Scripts - Curtain raiser (undated)
      Folder 40: Scripts - Het truth (undated)
      Folder 41: Scripts - Therapy scene (undated)
      Folder 42: Scripts - Trilogy (undated)
      Folder 43: Scripts - Family blinders (undated)
      Folder 44: Scripts - Retirement village (undated)
      Folder 45: Scripts - Susan's song (undated)
      Folder 46: Scripts - Coming out to mom (undated)
      Folder 47: Scripts - Party lines (undated)
      Folder 48: Scripts - Gay truth (undated)
      Folder 49: Scripts - Finale (undated)
      Folder 51: Ephemera (1983)
      Folder 52: Press and photographs (1983)
      Folder 50: Video (1983)
    - Committee: Education - Welcome to our Lesbian World audiovisual materials., 1983.; 1 betamax videocassette, 2 audio cassettes (Box 15)
      AUDIO
      One audio cassette labeled "Welcome to our World Lesbian Odyssey"
      One audio cassette "Welcome - 2nd Perf. (From Bar Area)" and "Sara's Birthday Song from Cast & Cheers."
      VISUAL
      One betamax videocassette labeled "Welcome to our Lesbian World SCWU 1983"
    - Committee: Education., 1980-1986. (Boxes 12,15, Folders 27 - 34, 53 - 54)
      Folder 27: Events, formerly entitled "LA/Valley's Educational Blockbusters (1982-1984)
      Folder 28: Lesbian Odyssey - Production materials, 1 of 2 (1985)
      Folder 29: Lesbian Odyssey - Production materials, 2 of 2 (1985)
      Folder 30: Lesbian Odyssey - Slides (1985)
      Folder 31: Lesbian Odyssey - Publicity and ephemera (1985-1986)
      Folder 32: Lesbian Odyssey - Applications (1985)
      Folder 33: Lesbian Odyssey - Correspondence (1984-1985)
      Folder 34: Lesbian Odyssey - Planning (1984-1985)
      Folder 53: Photographs (1980-1984)
      Folder 54: Miscellaneous (1982-1983), contains Education Committee roster, notes from theater productions, Central Education Committee minutes (April-May 1982), a folder from "A Women's Conference on Crime Prevention" with notes from Education meeting (June 7, 1982).
    - Correspondence., 1979-1987.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Flyers., 1979-1990.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Membership and employment., 1985-1987.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Newsletter., 1981-1994.; 14 folders (Box 13, Folders 3 - 16)
      Folder 3: 1981
      Folder 4: 1982
      Folder 5: 1983
      Folder 6: 1984
      Folder 7: 1985
      Folder 8: 1986
      Folder 9: 1987
      Folder 10: 1988
      Folder 11: 1989
      Folder 12: 1990
      Folder 13: 1991
      Folder 14: 1992
      Folder 15: 1993
      Folder 16: 1994
    - Photograph., 1982.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Contains one 3x5 inch color photograph labeled "Sally and Judy, 1982"
    - Research., undated.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - San Diego., 1981-1989.; Subseries 5.; 7.0 folders
    Contains flyers, newsletters, and miscellaneous material pertaining to the SCWU organization.
    - Flyers., 1985-1989.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous., 1981-1987.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Contains a clipping from the Lesbian News (September 1985) with an announcement of the San Diego chapter's meeting dates, order forms for SCWU watches, flyers for 1987 Camp SCWU and 1983 membership meeting.
    - Newsletter., 1986-1989.; 5 folders (Box 13, Folders 21 - 25)
      Folder 21: 1986
      Folder 22: 1987
      Folder 23: 1988
      Folder 24: 1989
      Folder 25: undated
  - San Gabriel Valley., 1980-1994.; Subseries 6.; 21.0 folders
    Contains committees' materials, flyers, newsletters, photographs, and miscellaneous materials related to the SCWU organization.
    - Committees., 1981-1982.; 4 folders (Box 13, Folders 26 - 29)
      Folder 26: Elections (1981-1988)
      Folder 27: Miscellaneous (1981-1982), contains drafts of committees' responsibilities
      Folder 28: Special interest programs (undated)
      Folder 29: Social (undated)
      Folder 30: Steering 1980-1986
    - Flyers., 1980-1989.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous., 1980-1988.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 32)
      Contains Bunny MacCulloch's membership card, received correspondence, Certificate of Appreciation from the San Gabriel Chapter of SCWU (1983), poetry, program from "The Sound of Music," sexuality questionnaire, activity questionnaire, clippings from the Lesbian News and the SCWU Newsletter, and San Gabriel Valley telephone tree.
    - Newsletter., 1981-1994.; 14 folders (Box 13, Folders 33 - 46)
      Folder 34: 1983
      Folder 35: 1984
      Folder 36: 1985
      Folder 37: 1986
      Folder 38: 1987
      Folder 39: 1988
      Folder 40: 1989
      Folder 41: 1990
      Folder 42: 1991
      Folder 43: 1992
      Folder 44: 1993
      Folder 45: 1994
      Folder 46: undated
    - Photographs., 1982.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 47)
      Contains one 5x5.5" color photograph and one 3x5" black and white photograph. Subjects and exact dates unknown.
  - Southern., 1979-1997.; Subseries 7.; 21.0 folders
    Contains newsletters, flyers, material from the Steering Committee, clippings, a photograph, and miscellaneous materials related to the chapter and the larger SCWU organization.
    - Committee: Steering., 1979-1985.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Clippings., 1979-1981.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 48)
      Includes one 3x5" black and white photograph of Judi Doyle, Bobbi Simon, and Judi's son, Brennan.
    - Flyers., 1979-1988.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous., 1979-1983.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Contains agenda of general membership meeting (November 13, 1983), "Let's Sleep on It" program, facilitator training packet, and "Southern Chapter Herstory" placard.
    - Newsletters., 1981-1997.; 16 folders (Box 13, Folders 50 - 65)
      Folder 53: 1984
      Folder 54: 1985
      Folder 55: 1986
      Folder 56: 1987
      Folder 57: 1988
      Folder 58: 1989
      Folder 59: 1990
      Folder 60: 1991
      Folder 61: 1992
      Folder 62: 1993
      Folder 63: 1995
      Folder 64: 1996
      Folder 65: 1997
  - Ventura/Santa Barbara., 1979-1992.; Subseries 8.; 10.0 folders
    Contains newsletters, flyers, Steering Committee documents, and clippings.
    - Clippings., 1979-1985.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Committee: Steering., 1980-1983.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Flyers., 1979-1986.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Newsletter., 1980-1992.; 7 folders (Box 13, Folders 72 - 78)
      Folder 72: 1980
      Folder 73: 1986
      Folder 74: 1987
      Folder 75: 1989
      Folder 76: 1990
      Folder 77: 1992
      Folder 78: undated